MATÍAS MONTONE

Full Stack Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina | +5491133501860 | matiasmontonedev@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/matiasmontone | https://github.com/matiasmontonee https://matiasmontone.vercel.app

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

22-year-old Full Stack Web Developer with knowledge in UX/UI Design. I always seek to grow as a professional and constantly update myself, with the aim of adapting and offering top-level digital solutions. Ability to work as a team and freelance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer | RO Medical

November 2024 - Present

- · Maintenance of back-office system to optimize processes and ensure system scalability.
- Optimization and refactoring of JavaScript and PHP code, achieving improvements in response times.
- Development of new sections in the system, enhancing usability and improving user experience.
- Real-time issue resolution, ensuring system availability and reducing downtime.
- Structured code documentation to guarantee efficiency and facilitate system maintenance.
- Collaboration with multidisciplinary teams to adapt the system to business needs.
- Contribution to system development, ensuring compliance with technical and business requirements.

Front-end Developer | WapiFirma

March 2024 - May 2024

- Front-end design of the page and collaboration with the Back-end.
- · Bug fixes and code debugging.
- · Constant maintenance and updates.
- · Interface design.
- User-oriented development and monitoring of its effectiveness.
- Structuring content semantically.
- · Web performance optimization.
- · API consumption to get and display data.

EDUCATION

Higher Technician in Web Design and Development

August 2021 - December 2024

Escuela Da Vinci

Content: RESS Web Page Development, PWA Mobile Applications, Content Creation, Execution of Digital Marketing Campaigns, APIs & Web Ecosystem, IoT.

SKILLS

Technologies and Software: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Vue, React, TypeScript, Node,

Express, Mongo, PHP, Laravel, MySQL and Firebase.

Tools: Git, Github, Photoshop, Illustrator, Wordpress, Canva and Office Package.

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native.

English: Upper intermediate (B2).